(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.2",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
おめかし中...
Getting dressed...
わぁー！
Waa!
皆さん、こんばんはー！
Good evening, everyone!
なー！
Naa!
ホロライブ5期生オレンジ担当アイドルVTuberの桃鈴ねねでーす！
I'm Hololive 5th Gen's orange idol VTuber, Momosuzu Nene!
本日はよろしくみんなー！
Everyone, please treat me well today!
わー！みんなこんねね！こんねね！
Wow! Hello Nene, everyone! Hello Nene!
さあ、いつもだったらね、なんかねねのライブといえば
Now, usually when you think of Nene's lives,
曲始まりなイメージがあるんですけど、
you'd imagine them starting with a song,
今日はですね、
but today,
挑戦したいことがありまして...
there's something I want to challenge myself with...
えー、実はですね、今体育館の舞台の上にいます！
Actually, right now I'm on a stage in a gymnasium!
おー！なぜみんなここに立ってると思う、
Oh! Why do you think I'm standing here?
えー、なぜ体育館だと思うか分かる人！
Does anyone know why it's a gymnasium?
すごい！おー、可愛い！可愛い！
Amazing! Oh, so cute! You're cute!
当てて！可愛いじゃなくて当ててほしい！
Guess it! I want you to guess, not just call me cute!
なんでだろう？発表する...なんかプレゼンテーション的なね、
Why is it? To announce... like a presentation of some sort,
ま、でもね、せっかく3Dライブで体が動くので、
Well, since I can move my body in 3D,
今回はなんと、
this time,
この後に控えてるライブのライブに向けて、
for the live performance coming up after this,
今からダンスの振り付けを1曲、この場で覚えて
I'm going to learn the choreography for one song right here
ライブに向かってみたいと思いまーす！
and then head to the live!
題して「ねねの挑戦！20分間で振りを覚えて
Title: "Nene's Challenge! Learn choreography in 20 minutes
ライブでパフォーマン」！
and perform it at the live"!
イエーイ！
Yay!
はい、というわけで今からですね、ねねが先生にですね、
Alright, so from now on, I'm going to have a teacher
ダンスの振りを教えてもらって、
teach me the dance moves,
実際にこの後のライブのセットリストの曲を
and then I'll actually learn one song
1曲まるまる覚えてパフォーマンスをしていきたいと思います。
from the setlist of the following live and perform it.
覚えきって成功するか、間違えて誤魔化しているのか、
Whether I'll learn it all and succeed, or mess up and fake it...
みんなにもね、分かるようにしていきたいと思いますので、
I want to make sure you all can tell,
ここで練習していきたいと思います。
so I'll be practicing here.
では、今日ね早速先生が来てくれてるんですけど、
Now, the teacher has arrived today,
あの、まいどん先生っていう、まいどん星から来てる宇宙人の先生なんですけど、
This is Maidon-sensei, an alien teacher from Planet Maidon,
なんか、いつもねねのダンスの振りを教えてくれてる先生なので、仲良く呼んでいきたいと思います。
She's the teacher who always teaches me my dance moves, so I'll call her over.
まいどん先生ー！
Maidon-sensei!
はーい！
Hii!
わー！まいどん先生！
Whoa! Maidon-sensei!
オデンガールズのまいどんです、お願いしまーす！
I'm Maidon from Oden Girls, nice to meet you!
イエーイ！オデンガールズっていうグループに所属してる
Yay! Maidon-sensei is part of a group called
まいどん先生っていうね、
Oden Girls...
あの、可愛いんだけど、今日ちょっとあれだね、宇宙人フォルムが強いね！
She's cute, but she's got a strong alien vibe today!
ほら、見えてますか？
Look, can you see her?
ちょっとね、ちょっとねねの様子入ってるんだよね。
She's got a bit of Nene in her.
ネッコ付いてたりとか、
Like having a Nekko (mascot)...
後ろにちょっとねねのリボンが付いてたりとか、
And a bit of Nene's ribbon on her back...
今日はね、このオレンジのまいどん先生がねねに、
Today, this orange Maidon-sensei
えー、ダンスを教えてくれます。
will be teaching me the dance.
お願いしまーす。
I'll be in your care.
はい、というわけで今日ねねが挑戦する曲なんですけど、
Alright, so the song Nene is challenging today is...
こちらになります！
This one!
Love Destiny / 堀江由衣
Love Destiny / Horie Yui
堀江由衣さんの「Love Destiny」という曲を
I'll be doing "Love Destiny" by Horie Yui!
やりたいと思います！イエーイ！
Yay!
これね、シスプリっていう、なんか
This is the opening for "SisPri", an anime
妹がいっぱい出てくるアニメのオープニングなんだけど、
where a lot of little sisters appear,
知ってますか？
Do you know it?
知らない。
I don't.
知らないかー。ちょっとだいぶ前のだからね。
You don't? Well, it's from a while ago.
覚えやすい？ちなみに振り付けは。
Is it easy to learn? The choreography, I mean.
大丈夫です。
It's fine.
大丈夫？本当に？あれ？もうちょっといつも元気じゃない？
Fine? Really? Wait, aren't you usually more energetic?
え、緊張してる？バレてる？
Uh, are you nervous? Is it that obvious?
緊張してますね。まずは、まいどん先生がお手本を見せてくれるらしいです。
You are nervous. First, Maidon-sensei will show us a demonstration.
私、まず踊ります。
I'll dance first.
フルで？
The full version?
フルで。
The full version.
あ、だからこのためにねね一回録音したんだね、歌を。
Ah, so that's why Nene recorded the vocals beforehand.
じゃあちょっと見せてもらおうかな。
Then let's see it.
ねねはここにいて見てればいいんだもんね。
I should just stay here and watch, right?
そうだね。
That's right.
オッケー。えー、じゃあ、行ってみましょう。まずまいどん先生の見本、レッツラゴー！
Okay. Then, let's get started. Maidon-sensei's demonstration, let's go!
会いたい　会いたい　会いたいのに
I want to see you, I want to see you, even though I want to see you,
会えない　会えない　今夜は
I can't see you, I can't see you tonight.
窓を打つ雨より　激しい嵐に揺れてる
Shaking in a storm more violent than the rain hitting the window.
会えない　会えない　会えないから
I can't see you, I can't see you, because I can't see you,
もっと会いたい　募るよ
I want to see you even more, it's building up.
燃え尽きてもいい　これが最後の真実
It's okay even if I burn out, this is the final truth.
初めての出会いは　平凡だったけど
Our first encounter was ordinary, but...
会うたびに　過去の誰よりも惹かれてく
Every time we meet, I'm more drawn to you than anyone from my past.
こんな気持ちのわけ　うまく言えないけど
I can't put the reason for these feelings into words well, but...
運命の恋と...
A fated love...
…最後の真実
...the final truth.
瞳閉じれば　二人になれる
If I close my eyes, we can be together.
今たとえこの部屋　一人でも It's my only destiny
Even if I'm alone in this room now, it's my only destiny.
逢いたい　逢いたい　逢いたい…
I want to see you, want to see you, want to see you...
あ、ここはできる！
Ah, I can do this part!
…のに逢えない　逢えない　逢えない　今夜は
...yet I can't see you, can't see you, can't see you tonight.
勝手に溢れてく
It overflows on its own.
激情は止められない
I can't stop this passion.
だから逢いたい　逢いたい　逢いたい…
So I want to see you, want to see you, want to see you...
ホッホ！
Ho-ho!
…だけど逢えない　逢えない　逢えない
...but I can't see you, can't see you, can't see you.
もう戻れはしない
I can't go back anymore.
あ、ここは繰り返しだね！
Ah, it's a repeat here!
これが最期の真実
This is the final truth.
ホイ！　ホイ！　ホイ！
Hoi! Hoi! Hoi!
誰かを想うとき…
When I think of someone...
あ、ここも繰り返しだ！
Ah, this part is a repeat too!
…苦しくなるなんて
...it becomes painful.
チュチュチュ！
Chu-chu-chu!
これまでの自分が
My former self
次々に崩れてく
is crumbling one after another.
ポーズとは裏腹
Contrary to my pose,
巻き込まれてゆく
I'm being dragged in.
あ、巻き込まれて、巻き込まれてる！
Ah, dragging in, I'm being dragged in!
見えない力で
By an invisible force,
引き寄せられてゆく
I'm being pulled closer.
フッフー！
Woo-hoo!
瞳そらさず
Without looking away,
二人になれた
we were able to be together.
あの夜の鼓動　忘れないで
Don't forget the heartbeat of that night.
次のサビもキレッキレにやって！
Do the next chorus with sharp moves too!
It's my last destiny
逢いたい　逢いたい　逢いたい…
I want to see you, want to see you, want to see you...
オッ！
Oh!
…逢えない　逢えない　逢えない　今夜は
...can't see you, can't see you, can't see you tonight.
ダンスダンスダンス！
Dance, dance, dance!
窓を打つ雨より
Harder than the rain hitting the window,
激しい嵐に揺れてる
I'm swaying in a violent storm.
逢えない　逢えない　逢いたいから
Since I can't see you, can't see you, I want to see you.
逢いたい！
I want to see you!
もうもっと　愛　愛　愛　募るよ
Even more and more, love grows.
燃え尽きてもいい…
It's okay to burn out...
サビは繰り返しなのかな？
Is the chorus a repeat?
最期の真実
the final truth.
あ、ここはできる！
Ah, I can do this part!
ねぇ不思議　彼を
Hey, it's strange, thinking of him
想って泣ける
and being able to cry.
夜があるなんて
That there are nights like this.
まるで love song
It's like a love song.
あ、できる！　ここできるよ！
Ah, I can do it! I can do it here!
あ、これね！　うんうん。
Ah, this one! Yeah, yeah.
まいどん先生の好きな動きめちゃ笑ってるｗ
Maidon-sensei's favorite moves are so funny lol.
だから逢いたい　逢いたい　逢いたい…
So I want to see you, want to see you, want to see you...
はい、もうサビ入ります！
Yes, going into the chorus now!
…だけど逢えない　逢えない　逢えない
...but I can't see you, can't see you, can't see you.
もう戻れはしない
I can't go back anymore.
ハイ！　ハイ！　できてるよ！
Hai! Hai! I'm doing it!
これが最期の真実
This is the final truth.
まいどん先生のステップとても好きだわ。
I really like Maidon-sensei's steps.
これよく見るｗ
I see this often lol.
あ、回るんだ一回。
Ah, you turn once.
決まってるよ！
It looks sharp!
おーー！
Ohhh!
どうですか？
How was it?
これをやるのね！
So this is what we do!
なんか途中でｗ
Something about the middle... (laughs)
まいどん先生の好きな動きあったくなぁ？
Did I have Maidon-sensei's favorite moves?
あったかもしれない。
Maybe you did!
間奏だね、ヤバいのは。
The interlude is the crazy part.
そうだね。基本繰り返しで。
Right. It's basically repeats.
うんうん、いける気がする！
Yeah, yeah, I feel like I can do it!
今から20分だもんね？
We have 20 minutes from now, right?
うん。
Yeah.
よしよし！
All right!
じゃあ早速覚えていきたいと思います！
Then I want to start learning it right away!
ねね頑張っていきます！　チャレンジスタート！
Nene will do her best! Challenge start!
よしよしよし！　時間ないからね！
All right, all right! We don't have much time!
えっと、最初まず曲が流れたら…
Um, first, once the song starts...
いい感じに乗る！
Get into the rhythm!
いい感じに乗る。オッケー。
Get into the rhythm. Okay.
いい感じに乗ったら…
Once you're in the rhythm...
最初からサビのこの振り付けなんだ、けど。
We start with the chorus choreography from the beginning.
あ、ここはね！
Ah, this part!
そうそう。もう踊れてそうなｗ
Yeah, yeah. It feels like you can already dance it lol.
これ、8の字にこう手を書いて。
Draw an '8' with your hands like this.
8の字ダンス
8-figure dance
右から、1、2、3、4。
From the right, 1, 2, 3, 4.
そしたら、この左手をなぞってく。
Then, follow with your left hand like this.
あ、そうそうそう！
Ah, I see!
1、2、3、4。ドン、ドン。
1, 2, 3, 4. Don, don.
いいいね！　そしたら反対。
Nice! Then the opposite.
1、2、3、4。
1, 2, 3, 4.
そしたらこう肩から、こうオーラを放つ。
Then, release 'aura' from your shoulders like this.
オーラを放つ！
Release aura!
1、2、3、4。ドン、ドン。オーラを放つ。
1, 2, 3, 4. Don, don. Release aura.
オッケー、オッケー！
Okay, okay!
最初からやると…
If we do it from the beginning...
1、2、3、4。左手見て。
1, 2, 3, 4. Look at your left hand.
はい！
Yes!
で、１、２、３、４、
Then, 1, 2, 3, 4,
勝ったからオーライ！
Kattakara alright!
あー、いいですね。
Ah, looks good.
勝ったからオーライ！
Kattakara alright!
あー、いいじゃん！
Ah, nice!
じゃあ、次ちょっと難しい。
Okay, the next part is a bit tricky.
トントン、ツッパ。
Ton ton, tsu-pa.
ちょっと待った。
Wait a second.
えーと、足は、チャンチャン、タッタ。
Um, for the legs, it's chan-chan, ta-ta.
右足を、あ、そうそうそう。
Right foot... Yes, that's it.
チャッチャ。
Cha-cha.
さあ。で、右手、左手、ワキワキ。
There. Then, right hand, left hand, waki-waki.
右、左、ワキワキ。
Right, left, waki-waki.
で、ヒラ、ヒラ、ヒラ、ヒラ。
Then, hira, hira, hira, hira.
ヒラ、ヒラ、ヒラ、ヒラ。
Hira, hira, hira, hira.
足は、こう右に出して、左に出す。
For the feet, step out to the right, then to the left.
あー、なるほど。
Ah, I see.
で、右手、左手、ワキワキ、ヒラ、ヒラ、ヒラ、ヒラ。
Then, right, left, waki-waki, hira, hira, hira, hira.
そしたら、タテ、ヨコ。
After that, vertical, horizontal.
タテ、ヨコ。
Vertical, horizontal.
そう。で、回る。
Right. Then, turn.
回る。
Turn.
のとき、こっち、あ、そうそう。で、足が、足が、
At that point, this way... Ah, yes, yes. Then the legs...
こう？
Like this?
そうそう。で、フリ、フリ。
Exactly. Then, swing, swing.
フリ、フリ。あー、いいね、いいね。
Swing, swing. Ah, nice, nice.
タテ、タテ、ヨコ。
Vertical, vertical, horizontal.
回る、で、フリ、フリ、フリ、フリ。
Turn, then swing, swing, swing, swing.
あー、オッケー、オッケー。
Ah, okay, okay.
じゃあ、こっから行くね。せーの！
Okay, let's go from here. Ready, set!
タンタン、ワキワキ、ヒラ、ヒラ、ヒラ、ヒラ。
Tan-tan, waki-waki, hira, hira, hira, hira.
タテ、ヨコ、回る、フリ、フリ...
Vertical, horizontal, turn, swing, swing...
はい、オッケー！
Yes, okay!
大体、大丈夫？このフリフリ。
Is the gist of it okay? This swing part.
これね。フリ、二回大きく、フリ、フリ、フリ、フリ。
This part. Swing, twice big, swing, swing, swing, swing.
あー、オッケー、オッケー。よし！
Ah, okay, okay. All right!
大丈夫。サビもう一回行くよ。
You're good. Let's do the chorus one more time.
行くよ。せーの！
Here we go. Ready, set!
タン、タン、タン、タン...左手見て。
Tan, tan, tan, tan... look at your left hand.
はい、はい、はい、はい！
Hai, hai, hai, hai!
勝ったからオーライ！
Kattakara alright!
チャン、チャン、ワキワキ、ヒラ、ヒラ、ヒラ、ヒラ。
Chan, chan, waki-waki, hira, hira, hira, hira.
タテ、ヨコ、回る、タン、タン...
Vertical, horizontal, turn, tan, tan...
まあ、まあ、うん。及第点、及第点。
Well, well, yeah. A passing grade, a passing grade.
まあ、まあ。そしたら、また繰り返し。
Well, well. Then, we repeat.
タン、タン、タン、タン...また左手見て。
Tan, tan, tan, tan... look at your left hand again.
反対。勝ったからオーライ！
Opposite side. Kattakara alright!
そしたら、今度右手を前に出して。
Next, put your right hand forward.
で、上げて。
And raise it.
あ、ここキメだもんね。
Ah, this is the signature pose, right?
そう。キメよりちょっと前かな。
Yes. A bit before the pose, I think.
タン、タン、タン、タン...で、これ裏側。
Tan, tan, tan, tan... then, the back of the hand.
手相見せて、やっぱ見せない。
Show your palm, then don't show it.
見せない。オッケー。見せて、見せない。
Don't show it. Okay. Show it, don't show it.
手相見せて、やっぱ見せない。そう。
Show your palm, then don't show it. Right.
で、えーと...右手、左手。
Then, um... right hand, left hand.
で、そう、そうそう。
Then, yes, yes.
で、真実...
Then, truth (shinjitsu)...
あ、ここね。
Ah, here, right?
あ、そうそうそう。で、パー、グー、グー、パー。
Ah, yes, yes, yes. Then, open, closed, closed, open.
結局、手相は見せる。
In the end, you do show your palm.
オッケー。見せる！パー、グー、グー、パー！
Okay. Show it! Open, closed, closed, open!
よし。そしたら、一回流してみるか。
All right. Then, should we try playing it through?
お、今日は物理的に流せるようにね。
Oh, today we can play it physically.
用意してもらってるんで。
We have it prepared.
じゃあ、まず最初いい感じに乗る。
Okay, first, get into the rhythm.
で、サビだもんね。そうそう。
Then it's the chorus. Right, right.
せーの！
Ready, set!
（ダンス練習中）
(Practicing dance)
8の字ダンス
Figure 8 Dance
あと１５分しかないよ。
Only 15 minutes left.
おっと。とりあえず、今サビができたね。
Whoops. Anyway, we've got the chorus down now.
そしたら、もうこれやったら、ねねさん得意のアイドルステップ。
Then, after this, Nene-san's specialty: the Idol Step.
あー、はい、オッケー。十万回。
Ah, yes, okay. 100,000 times!
アイドルステップ
Idol Step
ジョイマンにならずに、可愛く四回。
Don't become Joyman, just do it cute four times.
そしたら、Ａメロ、こっちにタン。
Then, Verse A, step this way.
Aメロ
Verse A
あ、ここ簡単だった。
Ah, this part was easy.
四歩、四歩行きます。チャン、チャン、チャン、チャン。
Four steps, four steps. Chan, chan, chan, chan.
三歩目から手を腰に。あ、そうそうそう。
From the third step, hands on hips. Ah, yes, yes, yes.
で、手、上げて、開いて、ドーン。
Then, hands up, open, and boom!
回転、ガラガラ、オープン、オープン。
Rotate, rattle-rattle, open, open.
四歩出てね。１、２、３、４、回転。
Step out four steps. 1, 2, 3, 4, rotate.
回転ガラガラ、オープン。
Rotate, rattle-rattle, and open.
そしたら...
And then...
ズンチャッ、ズンチャッ。
Zun-cha, zun-cha.
右足、あ、そうそう右足。
Right foot, ah yes, right foot.
ズンチャッ、ズンチャッ、タッタッタッタッ。
Zun-cha, zun-cha, ta-ta-ta-ta.
あ、2回だけ振って、あと胸。
Ah, shake just twice, then your chest.
ズンチャッ、ズンチャッ、タッタッ。
Zun-cha, zun-cha, ta-ta.
そしたらその足そのまま...
Then, with that foot as it is...
内、あー、外。
In, ah, out.
ジャンプ！ジャンプ！
Jump! Jump!
さあ今度手離して、内、外、ジャンプ！ジャンプ！
Now let go of your hands, in, out, jump! Jump!
イン・アウト・ジャンプの細かいステップ。
Detailed in-out-jump steps.
ズンッ、ズンッ、2回やったら蹴る。
Zun, zun, after doing it twice, kick.
蹴ると、ターン。
Kick, and then turn.
で戻る。ターン、ターン、でガッツだぜ。
And return. Turn, turn, then give it some guts.
いかつだぜ、そうそうそう、オッケーオッケー。
It's cool, yes yes yes, okay okay.
戻って、ガッツだぜ。
Return, and give it some guts.
ってやったら、その手そのまま前。
After that, keep your hands in front like that.
で、右手、左手、でぐるーっと回して。
Then, right hand, left hand, and rotate it all around.
あ、そうそう。ぐるーっと回して。あ、ここでここね。
Ah, yes. Rotate it all around. Ah, here it's like this, right?
そう、1回目、2回目終わるときに右足出す。
Yes, after the first time, when the second time ends, put your right foot out.
ほっ！そう。ほっ！そう。
Ho! Yes. Ho! Yes.
次に、次に入る。オッケー？
Next, move to the next part. Okay?
回転ガラガラ、オープン。
Rotate, rattle-rattle, and open.
内、外、ターン、内、外、ターン。
In, out, turn, in, out, turn.
ズン、ズン、蹴る。
Zun, zun, kick.
ターン、ターン、ガッツだぜ。その手そのまま。
Turn, turn, give it some guts. Keep your hands like that.
あ、そうそう、ターーン、ターーン、トッ、トッ。
Ah, yes, turn, turn, tap, tap.
ここがちょっと早い、タッタッ。うんうん。そう、はっ、はっ。
This part is a bit fast, ta-ta. Yeah. Yes, ha, ha.
Bメロ。反対、チャッチャッチャッ...
B-melody. Opposite, cha-cha-cha...
で左手、右手、開いて、ひとつひとつ。
Then left hand, right hand, open, one by one.
さあ、でこれ8回、1、2、3、4、5、6、7、8。
Now, and this for 8 times, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8.
そしたら、右手大きく回して、ドゥンドゥン、あ、そうそう。
Then, rotate your right hand largely, doon-doon, ah yes.
足はね、戻すね。ドゥン、ドゥン、あ、そうそうそう。
Bring your foot back. Doon, doon, ah yes yes yes.
タッタッタ、パッ。そしたらまたサビがくる。
Ta-ta-ta, pa. Then the chorus comes again.
はあー、オッケー。そうそうそう。
Whew, okay. Yes yes yes.
Bメロは、ターーン、ターーン、ズンチャッ...
The B-melody is turn, turn, zun-cha...
左手、右手、開いて、両手。ほーー。
Left hand, right hand, open, both hands. Hoo.
で1、2、3、4、5、6、7、8、ターン。
And 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, turn.
そこはあの改札通る感じ。
That part is like going through a ticket gate.
あ、スイカ。そうスイカ、あ、パスモでも可。
Ah, Suica. Yes Suica, ah, Pasmo is also okay.
ピッ。ズンチャッ、そう。ピッ。ズンチャッ、ダーー。
Beep. Zun-cha, yes. Beep. Zun-cha, daaa.
でサビ。うん、うん、あーオッケー。オッケーでしょ？
Then the chorus. Yeah, yeah, ah okay. It's okay, right?
曲でやろう。曲でやる。おんおん。
Let's do it with the music. We'll do it with the music. Yeah.
Aメロ、Aメロから、Aメロからいこう。
The A-melody, from the A-melody, let's start from there.
最後の真実。
The final truth.
で、アイドルステップ。ウン、ジャ、ウン、ジャ...
Then, idol step. Un-ja, un-ja...
右に、はじめての出会い。手、腰、最後、さあ。
To the right, the first meeting. Hand, waist, last, now.
オープンね、回転ガラガラね。見つめてるたびに。
Open, right? Rotate, rattle-rattle, right? Every time I look at you.
誰よりも輝いて。ズンチャッ、ズンチャッ。
You shine brighter than anyone. Zun-cha, zun-cha.
どんなときも。タッタッタッ、ツンツン。
Anytime. Ta-ta-ta, poke poke.
蹴る、戻る。じゃー。
Kick, return. There.
ガッツだぜ、ガッツだぜ。タッタ、タッ。
Give it some guts, give it some guts. Ta-ta, ta.
ぐるーー、右足出すよ。
Rotate, put your right foot out.
はい、ほっ、タッタッタッタッ、反対。じゃーじゃー...
Yes, ho, ta-ta-ta-ta, opposite. Jaa jaa...
左手から、両手。
Starting with the left hand, both hands.
1、2、3、4、5、6、7、8、取るよ。ピッ。ズンチャッ、ダーー。
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, take it. Beep. Zun-cha, daaa.
でこれ。おーー。このままいってみよう。
Then this. Ohhh. Let's keep going like this.
ヤヤヤ、今夜は。タッタ。あ、ひらひら。
Ya-ya-ya, tonight. Ta-ta. Ah, flutter flutter.
縦、横、ズンチャッ。もう一回。
Vertical, horizontal, zun-cha. One more time.
左手、反対。ガッ、タ、カ、ラ、オ、ラ。
Left hand, opposite. Ga, ta, ka, ra, o, ra.
いいなー、ここ。左手、タッ。
I like this part. Left hand, ta.
真実。アイドルステップ。
The truth. Idol step.
繰り返し、もしかして？そうなん。タッ。
Repeat, could it be? That's right. Ta.
ここの手がちょっと変わる。
The hand movement here changes slightly.
今度胸に。あ、苦しくなる。
To the chest now. Ah, it's getting painful.
でこれまた回転ガラガラ。オープン。
And here we rotate, rattle-rattle. Open.
1、2、3、4、
1, 2, 3, 4,
サビ
Chorus
5、6、7、8、
5, 6, 7, 8,
2、2、3、4、
2, 2, 3, 4,
次がちょっとクルクル... クルクル...
Next is a bit of spinning... Spin, spin.
違う！あはははは！
Wrong! Hahaha!
1、2、
1, 2,
はい、ガチだぜ！はい！
Okay, it's for real! Go!
1、2、3、4、
1, 2, 3, 4,
3、2、3、4、
3, 2, 3, 4,
クルッ、もう一回！
Spin! One more time!
クルッ、右足！はい！
Spin! Right foot! Go!
正解！
Correct!
フン、タッ、1、2、はい！
Hm, ta, 1, 2, yes!
左手から！
Starting with the left hand!
フン、はい！はい！
Hm, yes! Yes!
あ、もうできる、ここ。
Oh, you can already do this part.
1、2、3、4、5、6、7、8、
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8,
ズン、タッ、ドン、ドン、タッ。
Zun, ta, don, don, ta.
あ、またサビだ。
Ah, it's the chorus again.
あー、最高！
Ah, this is the best!
問題はサビのあとだね、ここね。
The problem is what comes after the chorus, right here.
ズン、タッ、ズン、タッ、ワキワキ、ヒラヒラ。
Zun, ta, zun, ta, Waki-waki, Hira-hira.
縦、横、うー！
Vertical, horizontal... Ooh!
よしよしよし、左手！
Yes, yes, yes, left hand!
ズン、タッ、ズン、タッ、はい、肩からオーラ！
Zun, ta, zun, ta, okay, aura from the shoulders!
いいな、今日一の出来な気がする。
Nice, I feel like this is the best I've done all day.
ズン、フンフン... でもここまで来たよ。
Zun, hmm-hmm... but we've come this far.
よしよしよし、アイドルステップだ。
Yes, yes, yes! Idol step!
でもこっからだったんだもんなー。
But it was from here on out, wasn't it?
ね、実はね、ここのCメロ...
Yeah, actually, this C-melody...
Cメロ
C-melody
Cメロはね、自由になってるんで。
The C-melody part is free-form.
あ、ラッキー！
Oh, lucky!
ね。だから、ねねさんの自由にこう、アドリブで...
Yeah. So, Nene-san, you can just ad-lib...
踊ってもらいます。
...and dance however you like.
へー、テテテテの、ここワンフレーズ全部？
Oh, so this whole phrase?
あ、そう、間奏前まで。
Yeah, until the instrumental break.
あ、オッケーオッケー、オッケー。
Ah, okay, okay, okay.
アドリブ
Ad-lib
フリーでやってもらって、で、次だよね、問題はね。
You'll do it free-style, and then comes the next part, which is the problem.
間奏のところ。間奏やってみようか。
The instrumental break? Let's try that part.
はい。で、間奏、間奏は、トン、トン、トン、トン。
Okay. Now for the instrumental break... Ton, ton, ton, ton.
間奏
Instrumental break
右手、左手、そしたら...
Right hand, left hand, then...
トン、トン、クロス、トン！
Ton, ton, cross, ton!
そう、そう、そう！
Yes, yes, yes!
ズン、タッ、ズン、タッ、クロス！
Zun, ta, zun, ta, cross!
やったら、巻いて、巻いて、払う！
Once you do that, roll, roll, sweep!
はっ、そう！
Ha! Like that!
ズン、タッ、ズン、タッ、クロス、巻いて、払う！
Zun, ta, zun, ta, cross, roll, sweep!
そう、そう、そう！そしたらこっから...
Yes, yes, yes! Then from here...
グォーーーン！
Gwoooon!
おーーーい！
Ooooi!
急な陽キャ。
Suddenly so upbeat.
おーーーい！さあ、右手、左手、クロス、巻いて、払って、グォーーーン！
Ooooi! Okay, right hand, left hand, cross, roll, sweep, and gwooon!
で、手、あ、そう、そう、そう！
And then your hands... Ah, yes, yes, yes!
で、1、2、3、4、5、6、7、8。
And, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8.
あ、そう、そう、そしたら「退きなさい」ってこうやって。
Ah, yes, yes, then do like this, "Move out of the way!"
あ、退きなさい。オッケー。
Ah, "Move out of the way." Okay.
で、あの、後ろ動画、いつもうちらがやってる...
And then that dance we always do.
ダダッ、ダダッ、ダダッ、ダダッ！
Da-da, da-da, da-da, da-da!
オッケー。あ、そう、ここの音ハメがあるから。
Okay. Yeah, this part hits the beats perfectly.
そしたらもうサビだよ。
Then it's back to the chorus!
はーい！間奏もう一回？
Yay! One more time for the break?
あ、一緒、一緒。
Yeah, it's the same.
オッケー。間奏もう一回やると...
Okay. Doing the break again...
ズン、タッ、ズン、タッ、クロス、巻いて、払って、グォーーーン！
Zun, ta, zun, ta, cross, roll, sweep, gwooon!
ズン、トン、トン、ズン、タッ... で「退いて」って。
Zun, ton, ton, zun, ta... and then "Move out!"
退いて！あ、そう、そう。
Move out! Ah, yes, yes.
で、ダダッ、ダダッ、ダダッ、ダダッ！
And da-da, da-da, da-da, da-da!
で、ここ、おっと！
And here... Whoops!
ちょっと音聞いてみようかね。
Let's listen to the music for a second.
大事、大事。大事だよね。
Important, important. That is important.
まあ、ここね、クルッてなってるみたいで...
Well, here, you're spinning around like this...
サビ
Chorus
おーい！アドリブ、アドリブ。
Ooi! Ad-lib, ad-lib.
ここまで自由。あ、ここまでオッケー。
It's free-form until here. Okay, until here.
せーの！ズン、タッ、ズン、タッ、... グォーーーン！
Ready, set! Zun, ta, zun, ta... Gwooon!
はい、トン、ドン、ドン、ズン、タッ、あー...
Yes, ton, don, don, zun, ta... ah...
ダダッ、ダダッ、ダダッ、ダダッ！で、ここ。
Da-da, da-da, da-da, da-da! And here!
なるほど、さあ。
I see! All right.
おほほほほ、いいじゃん。
Ohohoho, nice!
そしたら、なんと、最後は...
And then, believe it or not, finally...
このワキワキがない。えーー！？
The waki-waki part is gone! What!?
すぐ手相見せる。あ、歌詞的にないんだ。
Immediately show your palm. Ah, the lyrics skip it.
ジャン、ジャン、ジャン、ジャン、反対やって...
Jan, jan, jan, jan, do the other side...
肩からオーラやったら、手相見せる。やば、見せない。
Aura from the shoulders, then show palm. Oops, don't show it yet.
で、ズン、タッ、ズン、タッ、でもう最後。
And zun, ta, zun, ta... and that's the end.
ダダダダ、おわーー！
Da-da-da-da... Whoa!
アイドルステップして、はい、いい感じに乗る。
Idol step, and then get into the groove.
いい感じに乗る。オッケー。2回ずつ？
Get into the groove. Okay. Twice each?
2回ずつ、いい感じに乗る！
Twice each, get into the groove!
で、手を下からパーン、で、いい感じに回って。
Then throw your hands up, and spin around nicely.
で、あの、意味ありげなポーズ。
And then a meaningful pose.
大丈夫かな、Love Destinyを込めてね。
Is it okay? Put your "Love Destiny" into it.
オッケー、オッケー。え、もう終わった。あそこやりたいな。
Okay, okay. Wait, it's over already? I want to do that part again.
Love Destiny / 堀江由衣
Love Destiny / Yui Horie
振付師 まいとん
Choreographer Maito
わきわきのところ、サビの。
The waki-waki part of the chorus.
サビの？ 心配ね。
The chorus? I'm worried.
サビの？
The chorus?
そう、サビの。
Yes, the chorus.
あ、トントンわきわき、
Ah, tap-tap waki-waki,
右、左、わきわき。
right, left, waki-waki.
わき、わき。
waki, waki.
ヒラ、ヒラ、ヒラ、ヒラ。
Flutter, flutter, flutter, flutter.
で、縦横、
Then, vertical and horizontal,
で、回る。
then spin.
で、フリ、フリ。
Then, wave, wave.
あ、そう、そう、そう。
Ah, right, right, right.
あ、もう一回、もう一回！
Ah, one more time, one more time!
タチャン、チャン、チャン、チャン、チャン。
Ta-chan, chan, chan, chan, chan.
やばい、あと5分しかない！
Oh no, there's only 5 minutes left!
やばい！
Oh no!
右から、右、左、わきわき。
From the right, right, left, waki-waki.
ヒラ、ヒラ、ヒラ、ヒラ。
Flutter, flutter, flutter, flutter.
縦横、回る！
Vertical, horizontal, spin!
あ、そうそうそうそう。
Ah, right, right, right, right.
これを歌いながらやるってことですか？
You mean I'm supposed to do this while singing?
そうです！
Exactly!
まずい！
Oh boy!
もう口に出して必死なのに。
I'm already struggling just saying it out loud.
でも本番はまいと先生、ね？
But for the real thing, Maito-sensei, right?
前で、ね、見えないところで...
In front, you know, in a place where people can't see...
なんて？ なんて？
What? What?
ね、やってくれるもんね？
You'll do it for me, right?
いや、見てるよ。
No, I'll be watching.
あ、無理無理無理無理！
Ah, impossible, impossible, impossible!
ちょっと待って、あと5分。
Wait a minute, only 5 minutes left.
あと5分あります？
Do we have 5 minutes left?
あと3分！
Only 3 minutes!
あ、どうどうどう。ちょっと行こう。
Ah, what to do, what to do. Let's get going.
2番、2番から行こう。
The second verse, let's start from the second verse.
間奏までやれたらいいな。
I hope we can make it to the interlude.
はい。
Okay.
（歌唱：真実...）
(Singing: Shinjitsu...)
フッ、フッ、フッ、フッ...
Huh, huh, huh, huh...
誰かを想う時...
When I think of someone...
ヒムネショ、フッ、フッ。
Hum-ne-sho, huh, huh.
はい、回転グルグル。
Okay, spin round and round.
フッ、フッ、おー！
Huh, huh, oh!
はい、はい、はい、ジャン！ はい、はい、はい、ジャン！
Yes, yes, yes, jump! Yes, yes, yes, jump!
イン・アウト・ジャンプの細かいステップ。
Detailed in-out jump steps.
いいよ！
Good!
はい、クルクル、クルクル、フッ、フッ！
Okay, spin, spin, huh, huh!
はい、ガッツだぜ！ ガッツだぜ！
Okay, show some guts! Show some guts!
はい、手、トン、トン、ギュッ。
Okay, hands, tap, tap, squeeze.
クリアシドス、フッ、フッ、はい！
Clear-ashi-dosu, huh, huh, yes!
ヒラ、ヒラ、反対！
Flutter, flutter, other side!
ジャン、ジャン、ジャン、ジャン、ジャン、ジャン。
Jan, jan, jan, jan, jan, jan.
左手、右手、右手！
Left hand, right hand, right hand!
1、2、3、4、5、6、7、ピッ、ピタッ。
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, beep, snap.
うわー、ピ忘れてちゃう！
Wah, I forgot the 'beep'!
8の字ダンス
Figure-eight dance
反対、はい、カタカタ、オーラ！
Other way, yes, kata-kata, aura!
フッ、フッ、ヒラ、ヒラ、ヒラ、ヒラ。
Huh, huh, flutter, flutter, flutter, flutter.
縦横、フッ、フリフリ、はい。
Vertical, horizontal, huh, wave wave, yes.
8の字ダンス
Figure-eight dance
フッ、フッ、フッ、フッ、左手！
Huh, huh, huh, huh, left hand!
やばい、腰やばい。
Oh no, my hips!
手相見せて。
Show me your palm.
手相、あ、見せない！ 見せない！
Palm, ah, I won't show you! I won't!
フッ、フッ、真実。
Huh, huh, truth.
あ、ここ決まればね！
Ah, if we nail this part!
アイドルステップ
Idol step
アイドルステップ、でフリだよね。
Idol step, and then the wave, right?
そうだね、まるで出来た風に。
That's right, as if you've mastered it.
そうそうフリ。
Right, right, wave.
アドリブ
Ad-lib
ごまかしパーツね、ここ。
This is the 'faking it' part.
みんな見ようね、ここ見るところ。
Everyone, watch me! This is where you look.
見る所、見る所。
Looking point, looking point.
ん、ん、ん、ん、ん...
Mm, mm, mm, mm, mm...
あ、いいよ、いいよ、見てるよ、みんな。
Ah, nice, nice. Everyone's watching.
いいよみんな、あーあーあーあーあー。
Good, everyone, ahhhhh.
せーの、はい、はい、はい、はい、はい、はい、はい、はい。
One-two, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
ウェイ、フッ、フッ、フッ、フッ、フッ、はい！
Whee, huh, huh, huh, huh, huh, yes!
ジャン、ジャン、ジャン、ジャン、ジャン、ジャン！
Jan, jan, jan, jan, jan, jan!
8の字ダンス
Figure-eight dance
はい、はい！ あら？
Yes, yes! Huh?
逆になっちゃう、あれ？ ん、ん、ん、カタカタ、オーラ！
It's the wrong way, huh? Mm, mm, mm, kata-kata, aura!
よいしょ、ごめんなさい、あーー！
Heave-ho, sorry, ahhh!
フッ、フッ、フッ、真実。
Huh, huh, huh, truth.
あ、ここ決まればね、そう。まるで出来た風に。
Ah, if we nail this part, yeah. As if you've mastered it.
アイドルステップ
Idol step
で、2回ずつ、いい感じに乗るよ。
Now, two times each, get into the rhythm.
いいよ、はい、はい、はい、はい！
Good, yes, yes, yes, yes!
で、いい感じに回って、
And then spin nicely,
あ、いい感じに回って、
Ah, spinning nicely,
はい、意味ありげにポーズ。
yes, strike a meaningful pose.
大好きだもんね、意味ありげ。
You love those meaningful ones, don't you?
いいちゃん！ いいちゃん！
Nice, Nene-chan! Nice, Nene-chan!
5分、あ、終わったもう。
5 minutes... ah, it's already over.
あ、もう終わ...
Ah, it's already fin...
あ、というわけで終了のお時間だそうだ。
Ah, and so it seems time is up.
あ、どうかな？
Ah, how was it?
お水飲みたい！
I want some water!
お水、お水。ありがとうございます。
Water, water. Thank you very much.
あ、ホイッスル鳴ってしまった。
Ah, the whistle blew.
よしよしよしよし、どうどうどう？
Alright, alright, alright, how was it?
いや、割とありだよね？
Well, it was pretty good, wasn't it?
うん、全然行ける。
Yeah, we can totally do this.
あと割とごまかせてるしね、今日。
And we're faking it pretty well today too.
調子いいな、なんか。
I'm in top form or something.
全然いける。本当に。
You're doing great. Really.
任せて任せて。見ててね。
Leave it to me, leave it to me. Watch me.
あ、違う。
Ah, that's wrong.
ごめん、ちょっと軽くね、軽くやってもらうから。
Sorry, I'll just have you do it lightly, okay?
見ててね。
Watch me.
あーー！
Ahhh!
まあまあ、どうですか、みんな的に？
Well, how was it, everyone?
ごまかせる、いけるいける！
I can fake it, I can do it!
じゃあごまかし、ごまかして行こう！
Then let's go with the faking-it strategy!
お、でもね、この曲実はセトリ的に、
Oh, but actually, according to the setlist,
ちょっと真ん中の方に持ってきたくて、
I wanted to put this song in the middle,
一旦温めます、この曲を。
so we'll save it for later.
温めようか、じゃあ。
Let's save it then.
先生の体も今ポカポカなんで、
My body's all warmed up now too,
このまま、ね、ライブ会場に行って、
so we'll head straight to the live venue,
ねねのセトリがね、始まりますので、
and Nene's setlist will begin.
今からステージに飛ぶんだけど、
We're about to jump to the stage,
まいと先生はここで一旦お別れなんだけど、
and this is where I part ways with Maito-sensei,
一瞬飛んでもらったら、ねねが...
but if you jump with me for a second, Nene will...
まいどさんまで飛ばしてあげよっか？
Shall I send you back to Maido?
あ、いいんですか？
Oh, is that okay?
うん、いくよ？せーの！
Yeah, ready? One, two...
うわあああ！
Whoaaa!
まいど先生は無事にねねが飛ばしておきました。
Nene has safely sent Maido-sensei back.
よしよしよしよし。まいど先生を今帰宅させたんで。
There, there. Now that I've sent Maido-sensei home...
ここからはですね、ねねのライブパートをやってゆきたいと思います。
From here, I'd like to start Nene's live performance part.
ちょっとね、もう一回だけお水飲ませて。
Wait a sec, let me drink some water just one more time.
息を整えたら…
Once I catch my breath...
えい！ライブパートに入っていきたいと思います！
Hiyah! Let's get into the live performance part!
というわけで、桃鈴ねね誕生日2023、
So, Momosuzu Nene Birthday 2023,
毎日誰かの誕生日ライブスタート！
"Every day is someone's birthday" live, start!
hand in hand let's go party night
ココロ踊る　止められないの
My heart's dancing, I can't stop
泣いて　笑って
Crying, laughing
きみとの記憶　ずっと忘れない
I'll never forget the memories with you
Golden Time
作詞：大森 祥子
Lyrics: Shoko Omori
作曲：Kohei by SIMONSAYZ
Composition: Kohei by SIMONSAYZ
本当の自分はどこにいるとか
Wondering where my true self is
大人になるって大変で
Growing up is hard work
今は忘れてもいいかな
Is it okay to forget for now?
夜が待っているから
Because the night is waiting
心を弾ませ会える時を
Let my heart bounce as we meet
はしゃぎまわれば
And frolic around
伝えたい想いにいま
The feelings I want to convey, now
気づいてしまいそうで
I feel like I'm about to notice them
過去と未来　恐れていても
Even if I fear the past and future
からっぽのままじゃ動けない
I can't move if I'm empty
楽しめば It's all right
If I enjoy it, it's all right
はじめよう
Let's begin
ヤなこと全部忘れて
Forget all the bad things
きみと一緒に踊り明かせば
If I dance the night away with you
もっと素敵な自分になれる
I can become a more wonderful me
そんな気がするの
I feel like that
Let's get together 終わらないゴールデンタイム
Let's get together, an endless golden time
ぎゅっと近づくきみとの距離は
The distance to you gets closer
つかず離れず　回り道でも
Not too close, not too far, even if it's a detour
大切にしたい
I want to treasure it
夢見る自分はどこにいるとか
Wondering where my dreaming self is
未来なんてわからない
I don't know anything about the future
あるがままでいきたいの
I want to live just as I am
夜は待ってくれないから
Because the night won't wait for me
好きと嫌い　恐れていても
Even if I fear likes and dislikes
心はいま嘘をつけない
My heart can't lie now
伝えなきゃ Never give up
I have to tell you, never give up
はじめよう
Let's begin
ヤなこと全部忘れて
Forget all the bad things
恥ずかしさをかなぐり捨てたら
If I throw away my embarrassment
もっと素敵な自分になれる
I can become a more wonderful me
そんな気がするの
I feel like that
Let's get together 始まりはゴールデンタイム
Let's get together, the start is golden time
あのとき紡ぎ合った言葉
The words we spun together back then
それは確かに永遠に見えた
They certainly seemed eternal
夢のつづきね
It's the continuation of the dream
胸張って歩こう
Let's walk with our heads held high
はじめよう　目と目が合う瞬間
Let's begin, the moment our eyes meet
楽しいほど切なくなって
The more fun it is, the more bittersweet it gets
ぼーっとしてたら夜明けはすぐに
If I'm spacing out, dawn will soon
追いかけてくるよ
Come chasing after me
hand in hand let's go party night
ココロ踊る　止められないの
My heart's dancing, I can't stop
泣いて　笑って
Crying, laughing
きみとの記憶　ずっと忘れない
I'll never forget the memories with you
これからのことも
About things from now on
これまでのことも少しずつ
And things up until now, little by little
ちゃんとすべてを　受け入れられる
I can accept everything properly
信じられるきみがいるなら
As long as you, who I can believe in, are here
あーい！というわけで
All right! So...
ちょっと待って…音量調整して…
Wait a sec... Let me adjust the volume...
改めまして、みんなこんねねー！うおー！
Once again, hi everyone, Konnene! Whoa!
移動してきましたー。
I've moved to a different spot.
まずはですね、こちらも堀江由衣さんの「Golden Time」という曲を聴いていただきました。
First off, you just heard 'Golden Time' by Yui Horie.
イエーイ！
Yay!
このゴールデンタイムね、なんかまあまあ結構前の曲なんですけど
This "Golden Time", it's a song from quite a while ago...
ねねはこの曲ね、すごいなんかYouTube... 何で聞いたのかな
Nene, this song, I heard it on YouTube... I wonder where?
なんかアニメイトとかそういうのかな、で聞いて耳に残ってて
Was it Animate or somewhere like that? It stuck in my ear...
今回はやろうかなと思ってこの曲を選んでみました！
So I thought I'd perform it today and chose it!
そして、今日ちょっと遅くなってしまったんですけど
And, it's a little late today, but...
無事ねねの生誕祭を迎えることができました！
I was able to safely welcome Nene's birthday festival!
イエーイ！
Yay!
みんな改めてありがとうー！
Thanks again, everyone!
はーい。
Yes!
今回お誕生日ということで、お花をね、ステージのお花とかを
Since it's my birthday, I had many flowers on stage...
前回の2周年のときよりもいっぱい、いっぱーい咲かせてもらいました！
I had way, way more flowers blooming than last year's 2nd anniversary!
イエーイ！
Yay!
見て。なんか顔が付いてる花がいっぱい揺れてるでしょ？
Look. Lots of flowers with faces are swaying, right?
かわいい。キュートキュート。
So cute. Cute, cute.
なんとね、床にもね、あの、花びらが散ってると思うんですけど
And as you can see, there are petals scattered on the floor too.
なんか春っぽい感じでね、ライブ中も花びら舞っちゃったりなんかして
It has a spring-like feel, and petals might even dance around during the live.
エモい雰囲気が出ております。
It's creating a really emotional atmosphere.
今回はいつものあのスタジオじゃなくてね、今回違うところなので
It's not the usual studio this time, it's a different place.
なんか、あ、いっぱい人がいてもちょっと緊張するんですけど
So I'm a bit nervous with so many people, but...
頑張っていきたいと思います！
I'll do my best!
そして今回もロゴ作っていただきました。
And once again, a logo was made for the event.
桃鈴ねね生誕ライブ2023
Momosuzu Nene Birthday Live 2023
毎日誰かの誕生日というわけで。
With the theme "It's someone's birthday every day."
今日のハッシュタグはですね...
Today's hashtag is...
桃鈴ねね誕生日2023、こちらでたくさん呟いていただければと思います！
#MomosuzuNeneBirthday2023. I hope you'll tweet a lot with it!
みんなよろしくね。
Please support me, everyone!
頑張れ。あ、すげーって。はい、そうですよ。すごいよね、ステージ。
Do my best? Ah, "amazing". Yes, that's right. The stage is amazing.
次なんですけれども、ちょっとねねの休憩を挟みつつ
Next, while I take a little break...
ゲストパートに行きたいなと思っておりますので
I'd like to move on to the guest part.
今から過去のねねにパスをしていきたいと思います！
So I'm going to pass it over to the Nene of the past!
というわけでみんな、ゲストパーツ、あ、パーツじゃない。
So everyone, guest parts—no, not parts.
ゲストパート、レッツラゴー！
Guest part, let's-a-go!
はい！というわけで、ここからゲストパートに入っていくんですけど
Yes! So, we're entering the guest part from here...
え、ちょっとまだ誰が来るかね、わかんない。
Uh, I still don't know who's coming.
え、誰が来ると思うみんな？
Who do you think is coming, everyone?
いや、誰が、誰が来るんだろうな。
Man, who, who could it be?
いやみんなすっごいドキドキしてると思うんですけど...
I bet everyone's heart is racing...
ゲストね、3人来てくれて、あの一緒にね
Three guests are coming to...
今から歌って踊ってくれますので。
...sing and dance with me now.
いや本当誰が来るか、俺、本当に全然わかんない。えっ...
Seriously, I have no idea who's coming. Eh...
誰やろ。
Who is it?
そこらへんにおる奴。
Some guy over there.
全然わかんないんだけど...
I have no idea...
あれ運動してる奴おる。
Wait, someone's exercising.
誰か来てくれるんで、みんなすごい誰が来るかなーって
Someone is coming, so I'm sure everyone's...
ワクワクしてると思うんですけど。
...excited to see who it is.
えーじゃあ行っちゃいますか、とうとう始めちゃいますか。
Well then, shall we go? Shall we finally get started?
もしかしてゲストじゃない？
Could it be they aren't guests?
いやいやそんな、ねね立ち位置行くから。
No, no, wait, I'm going to my position.
ゲストはまだ来てないけど。
The guests haven't arrived yet, but...
誰やろ。
Who is it?
えっ、あ、誰やろな。あ、ちょっと...
Eh? Oh, who could it be? Ah, wait...
誰や！
Who is it!
俺や！
It's me!
あんじゃわしらか。
Oh, is it us?
じゃ、とりあえずうちらも立ち位置ついてみる？
Well, should we try taking our positions too?
できればうちら様ですか。
Are we possibly the ones?
やればできるかも。おお。
We might be able to do it if we try. Oh.
やればできるかも。
We might be able to do it if we try.
ハッピー☆マテリアル
Happy Material
作詞 うらん 作曲 大川茂伸
Lyrics: Uran / Composition: Shigenobu Okawa
光る風を追い越したら
If you chase the shining wind
君にきっと会えるね
I'm sure I can meet you
新しい輝き
A new brilliance
HAPPY READY GO!!
ねね！お誕生日おめでとうー！
Nene! Happy Birthday!
ありがとうー！
Thank you!
目覚めたばかりの
Just waking up...
ときめき弾けそう
My excitement is about to burst
胸ポケットに詰めて
Packing it in my chest pocket
空を見上げた
I looked up at the sky
前髪の行方を
The direction of my bangs
鏡とにらめっこ
Having a staring contest with the mirror
オリジナル笑顔で
With an original smile
駆け抜けたいよ
I want to dash through
1秒ごとドキドキ
Pounding every second
色づくこの日々が
These days turning into color
未来地図になる
Will become a map of the future
高鳴る鼓動
My heart beating fast
光る風を追い越したら
If you chase the shining wind
何が待っているのかな
I wonder what is waiting
雨降りでも平気
I'm fine even if it rains
虹になるよ
It will become a rainbow
カラフル HAPPY MATERIAL GO
Colorful HAPPY MATERIAL GO
君にきっと会えるね
I'm sure I can meet you
小さな勇気を咲かせよう
Let's make a little courage bloom
Oh...
ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！
Hi! Hi! Hi! Hi!
流行りも廃りも　要点チェックOK！
Trends come and go, essential points checked OK!
標的を確認　スピード勝負！
Target confirmed, it's a battle of speed!
喉越し爽やかな　特別な予感が
A refreshing feeling, a special premonition...
この胸あふれてく　加速してくよ
Is overflowing in my heart, and accelerating!
涙した笑顔　君は気付いてるね
The smile that shed tears, you've noticed it, haven't you?
恋しよ！　夢見よ！　私らしく
Let's fall in love! Let's dream! True to myself!
願いの先へジャンプしたら　受け止めてくれるかな？
If I jump towards my wish, will you catch me?
悩む前にできる事をしよう！
Let's do what we can before worrying!
カラフル☆ハッピーマテリアルGO！！　お揃いの煌めき
Colorful Happy Material GO!! Our matching sparkle!
君に届けたい　HAPPY READY GO！！
I want to reach you, HAPPY READY GO!!
光る風を追い越したら　何が待っているのかな？
If I overtake the shining wind, what will be waiting for me?
雨降りでも平気　虹になるよ
It's fine even if it rains, it will turn into a rainbow!
カラフル☆ハッピーマテリアルGO！！　君にきっと会えるね
Colorful Happy Material GO!! I'll surely be able to meet you!
小さな勇気を咲かせよう
Let's make a little courage bloom!
君に届けたい　HAPPY READY GO！！
I want to reach you, HAPPY READY GO!!
イェーイ！　わー！
Yeah! Whooo!
ねねね、お誕生日...
Nene-ne, happy...
...おめでとうー！
...birthday!
あ　そーれ！そーれ！そーれ！そーれ！
And here we go! Go! Go! Go!
なんで？　なんで？
Why? Why?
ねねさん、進行お願いします！
Nene-san, please lead the way!
えっと、今日はねぽらぼの皆さんに来ていただいてありがとうございます！
Um, thank you so much for coming today, everyone from NEPOLABO!
ありがとうございました！
Thank you very much!
違うよ！　うちらが来たんだから別にいいじゃんうちらは！
No! We're the ones who came, so don't worry about us!
え？　おめでとうございます！
Eh? Congratulations!
三人のゲストって誰だった？
Wait, who were the three guests?
みんなだったかも！
Maybe it was all of you!
わー！　知らなんだって！
Whoa! I didn't know that!
何だったのさっきのあれ？
What was that just now anyway?
これラミィのこれとか...何してたのあれ？
Lamy's movement here... what was that?
あれ最近ちょっと筋トレしてたから...
Oh, I've been doing some muscle training lately...
ここで？
Right here?
ステージ上でもやんだ！
Doing it even on stage!
やっぱいつでもどこでも筋トレしてこないと！
Well, you have to train anytime, anywhere!
意識高いなー！
So dedicated!
ちょっとさ、その自由な感じのスクショタイム欲しいと思うから...
Hey, I'd like to have a freestyle screenshot time, so...
みんな自由に写真を撮ってもらおう！
Let's have everyone pose freely for photos!
自由に写真を撮ってもらうの？
Take photos freely?
自由でいいの？
Is free okay?
芸術的っていう...
It's called artistic...
あ、いいよ。じゃあ、５カウントで！
Ah, okay. Then, on a 5-count!
５、４、３、２、１！
5, 4, 3, 2, 1!
私空いてた...
I was open...
倒れてきたもこれ！
This thing almost fell over!
５、４、３、２、１！
5, 4, 3, 2, 1!
詰めが遠くないね？
The final touch is missing, isn't it?
なんか！
Like!
なんなのこれ？
What is this?
５、４、３、２、１！
5, 4, 3, 2, 1!
ねぽらぼ仲良し！
NEPOLABO are such good friends!
面白い！
So funny!
最後だけ、空気読んで！
For the last one, read the room!
５、４、３、２、１！
5, 4, 3, 2, 1!
おめでとー！
Congratulations!
ありがとうね！
Thank you!
よかったのこんなので？
Was that okay?
めっちゃいいよ！
It was great!
失礼だな！
How rude!
バイバイ！
Bye bye!
帰って帰って！
Go home, go home!
こんな時間だよ！
Look at the time!
遅い遅い帰って！
It's late, go home!
最後まで映ろうとすんな！
Don't try to stay on camera till the end!
映り込みすんな！
Don't photo-bomb!
じゃあねみんな！
Bye everyone!
わー！
Whoa!
一本つかみ！
Gotcha!
あ、というわけでご覧いただきましたねぽらぼのみんなに来ていただきました！
Ah, and that was everyone from NEPOLABO who joined us!
たー！
Tada!
みんな自由ですごいよかったでしょ?
Everyone was so free, it was great, right?
選曲もねねね、めっちゃナイスな感じだったんじゃないかなーと...
Nene thinks the song selection was also a really nice touch...
思います！
I think!
では、ねねゲストパートの間で休憩もできたので、
Well, since I was able to take a break during the guest part,
次の曲に行きたいと思いまーす。
I'd like to move on to the next song.
よし、ちょっと整え直して。
Alright, let me just fix myself up a bit.
それでは聞いてください。ユキトキ。
Now then, please listen. Yukitoki.
陽の満ちるこの部屋
In this sun-filled room
そっとトキを待つよ
I quietly wait for the time
ユキトキ
Yukitoki
作詞：やなぎなぎ 作曲：北川勝利
Lyrics: yanaginagi Composition: Katsutoshi Kitagawa
気づけば俯瞰で眺めてる箱
Before I knew it, I was looking down at this box
同じ目線は無く
With no shared perspective
いつしか心は白色不透明
Before I knew it, my heart became white and opaque
雪に落ちた光も散る
Even the light that fell on the snow scatters
雲からこぼれる冷たい雨
The cold rain spilling from the clouds
目を晴らすのは遠い春風だけ
Only a distant spring breeze can clear my eyes
アザレアを咲かせて
Let the azaleas bloom
暖かい庭まで
To the warm garden
連れ出して 連れ出して
Take me out, take me out
なんてね
Just kidding
幸せだけ描いた
Portraying only happiness
お伽話なんてない
There's no such thing as a fairy tale
わかってる わかってる
I know, I know
それでもね
But even so
そこへ行きたいの
I want to go there
難しい数式
Difficult equations
誰も頼らず
Without relying on anyone
解いて明かしてきた
I've been solving and uncovering them
当たり前だって思っていたから
Because I thought it was natural
何も疑わなかったけど
I didn't doubt anything, but...
今 季節が終わろうとしても
Even now as the season is about to end
ついてくるのは自分の影ひとつ
The only thing following me is my own shadow
凍りついた道を
On the frozen road
花の雨で埋めて
Fill it with a rain of flowers
迷わないようにちゃんと教えてね
Show me the way so I don't get lost
奇跡だけで出来た
Created by miracles alone
完全結晶はない
There's no such thing as a perfect crystal
だからそう ひとつずつゆっくりと
So, that's right, one by one, slowly
手を繋いでいくの
Let's join hands
胸に貼りついたガラス
The glass stuck to my chest
溶けて流れる
Melts and flows away
光あふれる世界もうすぐ
A world full of light is coming soon
ひとりで守っていた
I was protecting it alone
小さなあの部屋は
That small room
少しだけ空いている場所があって
Has a little bit of empty space
ずっと知らなかったんだ
I never knew it
ふたりでもいいんだって
That it's okay for there to be two of us
わからずに待っていた
I waited without knowing
あの日はもう
That day is already over
雪解けと一緒に
Along with the thawing snow
春に変わっていくよ
It's changing into spring
透明な水になってそうしてね
Become clear water and do just that
アザレアを咲かすよ
I'll make the azaleas bloom
長い冬の後に
After the long winter
何度でも 何度でも
Over and over, over and over
陽の満ちる
Sunlight fills...
この部屋の中で
...this room
はい、というわけで聞いていただきました。ユキトキ。
Yes, and that was Yukitoki.
…の、雪解(ゆきとき)でした！
...That was Yukitoki!
みんな、どう？ 雪解は初挑戦なんですけど…
How was it, everyone? It's my first time trying Yukitoki...
良い感じ？
Was it good?
ちょっとこれ以外の… 文字のコメントが欲しい！
I want some... text comments besides these!
最高？ やったぁ！ よかった！
The best? Yay! Thank goodness!
えー、やったぜ！ ナイスだね！
Heh, I did it! Nice!
あ、最高すぎた、よかった！
Ah, it was too good, I'm glad!
『春を待つ木』が好きだからね
Because I like "The Tree Waiting for Spring"...
その、なんか、逆のバージョンっていうか
...so I wanted to try the "opposite" version of it.
そっちもいいなと思ってやってみたいと思ってました
I thought that'd be nice too, so I wanted to try it.
さあ、次はですね、あれをやっていきたいと思います
Now then, next, I'd like to do that.
さっきのね、これね、ねねの記憶力が試されるんですけど
For this one, Nene's memory will be tested...
みんなも覚えてる？ ねねが間違ってるかどうか
Do you all remember too? Whether you can tell...
判断できるのは、みんなの記憶次第だからね！
...if Nene makes a mistake depends on your memory!
というわけで… ちょっと待ってよ、えーっと…
So... wait a second, let's see...
ここ何だっけ？ ちょっと内田広由紀先生…
What was this part again? Wait, Uchida Hiroyuki-sensei...
こうで、ふわふわして…
It's like this, then fluffy...
ふんふん、回って…
Mm-hmm, and then spin...
あ、はいはい、オッケーオッケー
Ah, right right, okay okay.
うん、多分オッケー！
Yeah, probably okay!
よし、ほな、やってみましょうか！
Alright, then let's give it a try!
えー、いきます！ Love Destiny！
Here we go! Love Destiny!
Love Destiny / 作詞・作曲：伊藤千帆
Love Destiny / Lyrics & Composition: Chiho Ito
アイタイ Love Love Love Loveのに
I want to see you, love love love love, and yet...
アエナイ Love Love Love 今夜は
I can't see you, love love love, tonight...
窓を打つ雨より
More than the rain hitting the window,
激しい嵐に揺れてる
I'm shaking in a violent storm.
アエナイ Love Love Love Loveから
Because I can't see you, love love love love,
もっと Love Love Love 募るよ
The love grows even more.
燃え尽きてもいい
I don't mind burning out,
これが最後の
Because this is the final...
これが最後の真実
...this is the final truth.
初めての出会いは 平凡だったけど
Our first encounter was ordinary, but...
会う度に 過去の誰よりも惹かれてく
Every time we meet, I'm drawn to you more than anyone.
こんな気持ちの訳 うまく言えないけど
I can't put the reason for these feelings into words...
運命の恋と 人は呼ぶのでしょう
...but I suppose people would call it a "fated love."
ひとみ閉じたら ふたりになれる
If I close my eyes, we can be together.
今たとえ この部屋ひとりでも
Even if I'm alone in this room right now,
It's my only destiny...
アイタイ Love Love Love Loveのに
I want to see you, love love love love, and yet...
アエナイ Love Love Love 今夜は
I can't see you, love love love, tonight...
勝手に溢れてく 激情を止められない
I can't stop the passion that's overflowing.
だから Love Love Love アイタイ
That's why I want to see you, love love love...
だけど Love Love Love アエナイ
...but I can't see you, love love love.
もう戻れはしない
There's no turning back now,
これが最後の
Because this is the final...
これが最後の真実
...this is the final truth.
誰かを思うとき 苦しくなるなんてね
To think that loving someone would be so painful...
これまでの自分が 次々に崩れてく
The "me" from before is crumbling away.
ポーズとは裏腹 巻き込まれてゆく感じ
Contrary to my pose, I'm being swept away...
見えない力で 引き寄せられてゆく
...being pulled in by an invisible force.
ひとみそらさず ふたりになれた
Without averting our eyes, we became one.
あの夜の 鼓動忘れられない
I can't forget the heartbeat of that night.
It's my last destiny...
アイタイ Love Love Love Loveのに
I want to see you, love love love love, and yet...
アエナイ Love Love Love 今夜は
I can't see you, love love love, tonight...
窓を打つ雨より 激しい嵐に揺れてる
I'm shaking in a storm more violent than rain.
アエナイ Love Love Love Loveから
Because I can't see you, love love love love,
もっと Love Love Love 募るよ
The love grows even more.
燃え尽きてもいい
I don't mind burning out,
これが最後の
Because this is the final...
これが最後の真実
...this is the final truth.
ねえ 不思議 彼を想って泣ける
It's strange, I can cry just thinking about him.
夜があるなんて まるで Love song
That such a night exists... it's just like a love song.
Love Love Love 会いたい
Love, love, love, I want to see you
だけど会えない
But I can't see you
もう戻れはしない
I can't go back anymore
これが最後の真実
This is the final truth
あー、来てもらいました、まいどん先生！
Oh, we have Maidon-sensei here!
どうどうどう？ギリギリ大丈夫？
How was it? Was it barely okay?
いや本当もう、感想何もわかんなかった
Honestly, I had no idea how it went.
オリジナルがね、こうね、いっぱいあってぐちゃぐちゃになっちゃっててね
The original choreography... there were so many parts that it all got mixed up.
みんなが勝手から「オラ！」ってすごい書いてくるからさ、ちょっと笑っちゃった
Everyone was typing "Ora!" so much in the chat that I couldn't help but laugh.
でも、まいどん先生がニコニコ笑顔なの見えてて
But I could see Maidon-sensei smiling.
何点？100点満点中なら？
How many points? Out of 100?
可愛いから100点！
100 points because you're cute!
やったー！これからもよろしくお願いします
Yay! I look forward to working with you.
というわけで、まいどん星からやってきたおでんガールズのまいどん先生でした！
And so, that was Maidon-sensei from the Oden Girls who came from Planet Maidon!
ありがとうございましたー！
Thank you very much!
バイバーイ！頑張ってね！
Bye-bye! Good luck!
はい、というわけで、ねねも次の曲に向けてちょっとお着替えしていきたいと思いますので
All right, so Nene is going to change for the next song...
一旦、はけます！オッオッオッオッオッ...
So I'll step out for a moment! Ho-ho-ho-ho...
じゃーん！いぇーい！見てみんな！
Ta-da! Yay! Look everyone!
こないだの4thフェスの時にお披露目したばかりのブライト衣装になります！
This is the Bright costume that was just unveiled at the 4th Fes!
この服を着て、次はちょっとここの先、実はステージがありまして
Wearing this outfit, next, there's actually a stage further ahead...
そこをびーんと前に行って歌っていきたいと思います！
And I'm going to go right out there and sing!
テッテッテ、うわー見て見て、根っ子花道！そして、これはなんだ！？べーん！
Step by step... Wow, look, it's a "Nekko" runway! And what's this? Ta-da!
いぇーい！わー！うわー！はいどうも、ハイタッチどうもどうも
Yay! Wow! Whoa! Hello, high-fives, hello, hello.
いつも応援ありがとうございます、桃鈴ねねでございます！
Thank you always for your support, I am Momosuzu Nene!
というわけで、真ん中のステージでも一曲聴いていただきたいと思います
And so, I'd like you to listen to one song from the center stage.
それでは聴いてください、一番の宝物
Now, please listen to "Ichiban no Takaramono".
裾が濡れたなら
If the hem gets wet
乾くの待てばいい
I just have to wait for it to dry
水音を立てて跳ねた
Splashing with the sound of water
君が教えてくれたんだ
You were the one who taught me
もう怖くない
I'm not afraid anymore
握っていてくれた
You held on to me
この手を離さなきゃだめだ
I have to let go of this hand
ひとりでもゆくよ
I'll go, even if I'm alone
たとえ辛くても
Even if it's painful
みんなで見た夢は
The dream we saw together
必ず持ってくよ
I'll definitely take it with me
みんなとがいいな
I want to be with everyone
みんなとがよかった
It was good to be with everyone
でも目覚めた朝
But on the morning I woke up
誰も居ないんだね
No one was there
もう振り返っても
Even if I look back
誰の影もない
No one's shadow remains
水たまりだけが 光った
Only the puddles shined
生きていくこと
To live
それは立ち向かっていくこと
That is to stand up to challenges
それがわかったなら
If I've understood that
あとは踏み出す勇気だけ
All that's left is the courage to take a step
どこまでもゆくよ
I'll go anywhere
ここで知ったこと
With what I learned here
幸せという夢を
The dream called happiness
叶えてみせるよ
I'll make it come true
みんなと離れても
Even if I'm apart from everyone
どんなに遠くなっても
No matter how far away I get
新しい朝に
In the new morning
この僕は生きるよ
I will live on
ひとりでもゆくよ
I'll go on alone
死にたくなっても
Even if I want to die
声が聞こえるよ
I can hear a voice
死んではいけないと
Saying I must not die
たとえ辛くても
Even if it's painful
闇に閉ざされても
Even if I'm shut in darkness
心の奥には
In the depths of my heart
明かりが灯ってるよ
A light is lit
巡って流れて
Time has passed and flowed by
時は移ろいだ
The seasons have changed
もう何があったか
I can't remember
思い出せないけど
What happened anymore, but...
目を閉じてみれば
If I close my eyes
みんなの笑い声
I hear everyone's laughter
なぜかそれが今
For some reason, that's now
一番の宝物
My most precious treasure
ありがとうございましたー！
Thank you very much!
どー？
How was it?
エモエモエモいね！
It's so, so, so emotional, right?
というわけでここでみんなのテンションぶち上げのところで
So, while everyone's tension is through the roof...
まだラスト1曲あるんですけど、その前にグッズの紹介させてください！
We still have one last song, but before that, let me introduce the merchandise!
こちらー！
Here it is!
あ、こっち！
Oh, this way!
桃鈴ねね誕生日記念2023のグッズが出ます！イェーイ！
Nene Momosuzu Birthday Celebration 2023 goods are coming out! Yay!
こちらー！
Here it is!
ドドーン！アクリルジオラマスタンド、ランダムアクリルキーホルダー
Tada! Acrylic diorama stand, random acrylic keychains...
ねねぬいぐるみ、そして記念ASMR2種類！
Nene plushie, and two types of commemorative ASMR!
これ、あまあまと、からからの2種類のASMRです。
These are 'sweet-sweet' and 'dry-dry' ASMR.
他にもあります。そして、
There's more. And,
特典のポストカード、一個ずつ見ていきましょう。
the bonus postcard, let's look at them one by one.
こちら、
This...
カニビーム先生に描いていただきました、アクリルジオラマスタンド！イェーイ！
is the acrylic diorama stand drawn by Kanibiimu-sensei! Yay!
なんかパーティー風でね、なんかピッピッピって感じで、
It has a party vibe, like, pip-pip-pip,
すごい可愛い感じでしょう？
isn't it super cute?
これちょっと、えーらす曲の匂わせです。
This is a bit of a teaser for the last song.
次！
Next!
えー、JAZZ JACK先生に描いていただきました、
Um, drawn by JAZZ JACK-sensei,
ランダムのアクリルキーホルダーになります！
it's the random acrylic keychains!
可愛い！見てみて！
Cute! Look!
いろんなね、いろんな表情で描いていただきました。
They're drawn with various expressions.
こちらね、チェーンの部分も桃になってて、
The chain part is also a peach,
ねねらしさが出てて可愛いと思うので、ぜひチェックしてください。
and I think it's cute and very Nene-like, so please check it out.
そしてこちら！
And this!
桃鈴ねねのぬいぐるみです！
It's the Momosuzu Nene plushie!
今ね、ホロライブ公式でもぬいぐるみ出てるんですけど、
Currently, there are plushies from Hololive official as well, but
それとは別で、ねねからも人形が出ます。
apart from that, a doll is coming out from Nene too.
こちらは、アウターのね、着脱が可能になってますので、
For this one, the outer garment is removable, so
脱がせてみたり、着せてみたり、
you can take it off or put it on,
そんなことをしながら、みんなのお好みのよにカスタムして、
while doing things like that, customize it to your liking,
あのね、次のライブとかあったらこうやって振って欲しいななんて思っております。
and I hope you'll wave it like this at the next live or something.
そして！フルセットを購入してくれた人には、なんと...
And! For those who purchase the full set, it's...
久しぶりの直筆サイン！イェーイ！
been a while, but you'll get a handwritten autograph! Yay!
そして箔押しの...
And a foil-stamped...
複製メッセージ入りのポストカードをプレゼント、
duplicated message postcard as a gift,
あ、じゃないや、つけさせていただきます。
oh no, we'll include it.
ねねがいっぱい、あの丹精込めて一枚一枚書きますので、
Nene will put a lot of heart into writing each and every one,
よかったらチェックよろしくお願いします。
so please check it out.
さて、次で最後の曲になるんですけれども、
Now, the next one will be the last song, but
次は...新曲です！イェーイ！
next is... a new song! Yay!
めっちゃね、楽しい感じでワクワクでルンルンな感じの曲ですので、
It's a really fun, exciting, and happy song, so
みんなで楽しんでもらえたらなと思います。
I hope everyone enjoys it.
それでは、聞いてください。
Now, please listen.
あ、オーケーオーケー。
Oh, okay, okay.
それでは聞いてください。
Now please listen.
コングラッCHU☆マーチ！
Congrats CHU☆March!
コングラッCHU☆マーチ
作曲：yuzen (Hifumi,inc.)
作詞：真利 -himari- (Hifumi,inc.)
Congrats CHU☆March
Composition: yuzen (Hifumi,inc.)
Lyrics: Himari (Hifumi,inc.)
あ〜あ朝、目が覚めたら
Ah, in the morning, when I wake up,
枕のそばに
by my pillow,
帯付きの5000兆
5 quadrillion yen in bundles
添えられてだらいいな
it would be nice if it were there.
あ〜あ3食 昼寝あり
Ah, three meals and a nap,
できることなら
if possible,
おやつ付き大企業
a large company with snacks,
コングラッCHU 社長出勤
Congrats CHU, CEO's late arrival.
全体祝え！
Celebrate, everyone!
生まれてきた今日におめでとう
Congratulations on being born today.
今日、明日、明後日
Today, tomorrow, the day after,
毎日誰かの誕生日
it's someone's birthday every day.
祝福のベル鳴らしたら
If you ring the bell of blessing,
笑顔全開
smiles at full blast.
月曜はおやすみ
Mondays are off,
水曜もなしで
no Wednesdays either.
不労所得 毎日ボーナス
Unearned income, daily bonuses.
そうだ！明日も何かの
That's right! Tomorrow too,
祝日にしよう そうしよう
let's make it a holiday of some kind. Let's do that.
異世界からやってきた
I came from another world
憧れと希望胸にこの場所
with longing and hope in my heart to this place.
歌って 踊って
Sing and dance
全世界届けましょう
and let's reach the whole world.
届けましょう
Let's reach out!
あ〜あ朝、起きるだけで
Ah, in the morning, just for waking up
褒められたいな
I want to be praised.
誰にも見せてない才能
The talent I've shown no one,
そろそろ出してやるか
maybe it's time to show it off.
あ〜多分いる神様
Ah, the God who probably exists,
聞こえてますか？
can you hear me?
願ってるこの願い
This wish I'm wishing,
すべてを叶えてくれー！
grant them all!
全体祝え！
Celebrate, everyone!
お礼はこの歌でって事でいいよね
Let's just say this song is my thank you,
ありがとう！
thank you!
今日　明日　明後日
Today, tomorrow, the day after...
毎日誰かの
Every day is someone's...
誕生日祝福の鐘
Birthday! If the bells of blessing...
鳴らしたら笑顔咲け
...ring, let smiles bloom!
ロケットを作って
Let's build a rocket...
どこまでも行こう
...and go wherever we want!
宇宙旅行　月すら超えて
Space travel, even beyond the moon!
そうだ！明日も誰かの
That's right! Tomorrow, let's...
お祝いをしよう　そうしようっ
...celebrate someone again! Let's do it!
みんな　みんな　おめでとう！
Congratulations to everyone, everyone!
ありがとうございましたー！
Thank you so much!
新曲「コングラッCHU☆マーチ」でしたー！
That was my new song, "Congratu-CHU☆March"!
いかがでしたか？
What did you think?
可愛いっしょ？
It was cute, right?
え、そして、この後は、
And, after this...
21時15分くらいから
...from around 21:15...
え、この曲のですね、あの、MVが、あの、発表になります！
...the music video for this song will be released!
後ろがね、こんな感じで
The background looks like this...
可愛い感じになってるので、一緒に見に行きましょう。
...and it's so cute, so let's go watch it together!
これ見て作ってもらったー。
They made it based on this!
え、そして、そのあと、21時半くらいからは、
And after that, from around 21:30...
メンバーシップ限定で、え、お疲れ様のアンコール会、
...it'll be a membership-exclusive encore party...
そしてブライト衣装をじっくり舐め回す会、
...and a session to appreciate every detail of the Bright costume...
行いたいと思いますので、
...so I'll be holding those...
よかったら会いに来てください！
...so please come see me if you'd like!
というわけで、みんな、今日は最後まで見てくれてありがとう！
So, thank you everyone for watching until the very end today!
せーの、まったねー！
One, two... see you later!
これからもよろしくー！
I'm counting on you from now on, too!